Brigham Jenkins (the case system): Good afternoon we're just going to give it another minute for others to join, maybe another two minutes and then we'll get started.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): All right, let's go ahead and get started.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): My name is brigham and I will be training you today on customs editor in file fine if at any point you can't hear me my Internet cuts out or Mike just stops working, please let me know in the chat or you can unmute yourself, and let me know that way that works as well.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): I do ask that, throughout the training that you stay muted, simply because we are recording we want to.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): Make sure there aren't any unnecessary background noises.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): For when you later listen to this training.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): If you do have any questions, please don't hesitate to either use zoom chat or unmute yourself and ask that way they both work for me i'm fairly easy going.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): feel free to follow along as well as we go a few things we're covering today we're going to go over your sections, how you can customize them personalize them we'll go over your vitals.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): Which is your crucial data in your project.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): How to modify those and add new vitals will also go over your phases.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): How to add or take away phases, which is just what stage your project or your cases at.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): Its lifespan and then we'll go over folders in your folder structure.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): So when you're in file vines, the advanced tools, at least for me, I personally like to have two tabs open.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): One tab will be in one of my projects and then the other tab will be in the advanced tool, so I have to open here.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): The second one, if I were to try to navigate to advanced.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): Through my main menu.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): And then come to customs editor.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): Here I type out an order his name.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): However, yours, if you only have one organization should automatically be applied here.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): will select the project tight, if you have multiple.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): And here we are, we have our sections vitals phases and folders.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): Now, going back into my project just to reiterate exactly what these are all of these on the left hand side are our sections case summary section activity section medical section, etc.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): up here in the blue, we have our vitals.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): So, as we can see a lot of this crucial data, this is incident date as well dates incident types.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): Maybe the primary attorney and the intake are.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): All scattered throughout our project in various sections, but located Nice and neatly up here for us to view quickly.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): we'll go over phases so right here on the top rate.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): And then, our folder structure which is located in the Doc section now some people like to rename their Doc sections like filing cabinet right or something along those lines, I prefer docs or maybe documents.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): were talking about these folders here.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): So whenever we create a new project will have this beautiful folder structure and we won't have to come in and create new ones, one by one.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): So in the advanced tool.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): In customs editor This is where we create new sections like clipping section, or we can scroll through and Edit existing ones.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): For today i'll go ahead and Edit this case summary section.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): For the name of the icon if you were to create a new one, of course, you'll give your section a name.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): And then you'll click this little icon.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): which will allow us to that view and select.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): an icon we have many to choose from.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): So maybe case summary i'll switch it to this nice little folder there.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): The section selector it's automatically going to fill in depending on what you put in the name.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): Alright, so if I come up here, create a new section.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): See how this section selector automatically gave itself a name, so we don't want to touch the section select here.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): we'll just let that be.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): The default section visibility, this allows us to either always see the section or always hide it.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): And then we have initially visible in hidden, which means initially when we create a project if it's invisible we're going to see it, but then later we can go in and turn it off.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): Right same with initially hidden when a new project is created the section won't be here it won't be visible, but I can go in and turn it on.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): let's see if I can find one that's.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): Initially visible or hidden for us.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): Alright, so this negotiate settlement section properties, I have, as initially visible we call these FLEX sections because they're flexible.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): So if I go back to my project, we can see that it's here negotiate settlement.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): But if I go into managed sections and the very bottom left.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): We can see these are toggled on so that negotiate summit it's additionally visible so it's going to be green I can go ahead and click it and now it's off we don't see it along with workers COMP right so negotiated settlement, we see just kind of disappears.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): All right, yeah just person that section would be the same thing.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): Right you'd be able to toggle them on and off as long as they are either initially visible or initially hit.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): We won't be going over today the different types of sections that you can have such as an intake disbursement.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): Case summary expenses right we'll just go over how we can navigate through the back end.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): But if, at the end, we have any extra time, I think, maybe we can go over some of those questions pertaining to your specific build but that's more of a an icy type of question.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): because everybody is different every firm is different, as to how they want to do things.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): But yeah you could easily hit this section and create a disbursement right.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): Always visible or initially visible right give it some notes, if you want just to describe what this section is about and then section type is going to be custom.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): So we have built in sections.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): such as the docs section, the activity section, and we can see them right here, they say built in if I scroll down, we have reminders or deadlines calendar they're all built in those we can't really customize other than the name of the icon.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): right we don't add fields or widgets or anything like anything of the sort, however, something like the case summary.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): it's a custom section so we're able to add fields and widgets.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): So a field in file vine if I go to my case summary would be something like this document generation button here, well, this would be a widget or this Doc Jen would be a widget this task low.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): button here task will trigger would be a widget but then fields would be something like this primary attorney field, which is a person field right, where we have the statute of limitations.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): Is caption plaintiffs they filed, these are different fields so that's what we're talking about.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): When we say we create custom fields or custom widgets.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): So when we click this plus.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): We get this template here.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): Where we can select field will create a field and will create a widget as well, but when we select the field type, we can see, there are several to choose from.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): So maybe right now we can do a drop down list.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): And then the prompt we just give it a name.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): So drop down.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): The field selector just like our section selector is going to automatically fill out we don't need to worry about this.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): And then, because this is a drop down field we're going to have options to choose from.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): So i'll just put in a few here.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): And then my advanced properties when you're first creating fields this advanced properties, is going to be collapse like this, so if we were to.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): Open that up.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): expand it, we have the ability to place this field where we want it in our section.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): So the row and the order in row.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): would be like you see on an excel sheet, so this would be row one this is be row to row, three, four, etc, the order and row would be like your column, this would be ordering road 0123 etc.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): So right now it's going to default place it at the very bottom of your section any new field you create the system is going to put it at the very end.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): But if we wanted to adjust this I can not come adjust it later, but at least for now i'm just going to keep it at the bottom.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): The visibility.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): This means that we're making it contingent.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): On another field, or we can so we can show it always or we can show it when another field.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): So maybe I want we'll just say the case number.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): contains.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): A one sure and i'll give you a better example here shortly, as to why you might want to make something contingent, but just for the sake of making a contingent there we go.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): So if the case number of field has a one in the field as its value.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): This field going to show up so required means that you cannot save.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): This section, unless you fill out this field.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): locked means only project admins can make changes to the field or add values obsolete is kind of like deleting a field.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): But if there's already a value inside of that field and, later on, you want to come and remove it marketing obsolete will continue to keep the values in that field, but any new project or existing project that doesn't have any data in it it's going to show, as if it doesn't exist.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): And I can show you what that looks like as well.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): So we have to drop down list like create and then i'll go back to my other tab another reason why I like to have two tabs open, so I can keep going back and forth.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): And I know I don't have to worry about these arrows So if I go to the very bottom.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): it's not here.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): However, if I come up and in case number, we remember it just has to have a one in here so i'll put a one here.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): Safe i'll go to the bottom.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): And now we have our test drop down.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): field wasn't here before, however, nowadays.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): And I don't have to save it.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): For that field to appear or disappear all right, so we can see it's not here, but once I put one.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): come down now, it shows up so maybe a reason why you might want to make guilds contingent contingent on others would be.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): like an example like this, this workers COMP case if I select Yes, this is workers COMP case.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): I now have this workers COMP information that I should fill out right.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): Whether or not they had surgery panel physicians.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): Whatever these other fields are pertaining to workers COMP right, but if it's not a workers COMP case I don't need to worry myself with that information flooding my screen right just taking up space.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): So that would be a reason why I run a contingent.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): feel.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): So coming back in and let's say actually with this test drop down.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): I told them, I told you all that we were going to move it so let's move it to a different location.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): I think we should move it.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): Right above key dates.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): So let's go back into our customs editor and now I want to look for that he dates field.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): Here it is it's that sub section header and we noticed that it's on row 36.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): So that's road 36 order and rose zero.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): So I do want to put it right above it so we want to put this on road 35 so go back down to my field that we created.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): come down to advanced properties.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): Just make sure this is 35.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): hit update, but I come back here my project, and I refresh the page.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): We see test drop down right above the key thing there.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): So that's how I would go about moving around your different fields in the widgets.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): Now this little arrow.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): This is really important, so like right here, we see between case number and judge.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): There isn't any space to place a field right because we can't put something in row 75.5.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): So what we do here is we create space on the back end by clicking this button this pushes as we can hover and we we see what it actually does it pushes this field and all other fields down a row.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): So if I click that you see this POPs to 77 and everything else follows suit, so now we have row 76 to work with.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): This doesn't cause any white space in your project.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): Right, the ui will not change this is just creating space on the back end so I can do this as much as I want.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): And it's not going to affect how it looks on the front end.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): But now we're just giving yourself space between 76 and 79 to place new fields.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): So widgets are going to work pretty much the exact same.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): When I click on a widget I select the type we have Doc generation buttons instructions, if you want to have instructions that on to maybe how to fill out a field.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): Give somebody an instruction There we have report fusion widgets subsection headers, which is what that key date is and litigation right and it comes with these nice little lines to kind of separate.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): These sections or sub sections from each other.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): But we also have this action button, which comes with extra types, such as the link to another website sending an email were extending to quickbooks or even a task flow trigger.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): you'll go over more the task flow triggers in your task flow training deadline chains and task flows so for right now we'll just do a link but.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): The prop, of course, is just the name.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): The widget selector fills itself out.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): would give this an icon so maybe instead of scrolling through and finding one I can just type out a key word right here at the top, such as link.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): And it's going to give me some.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): icons that are the other contain the word link.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): or they're close enough right like an anchor or chain.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): Best practice when creating a widget is to click this same as widget name, you can give your widget a different name if you'd like to.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): However, if you do the prompt on the ui and the front end is going to show test link in your project.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): But in customs editor it's going to show up as a new name right, and so it might cause a little bit of confusion as to what that field is actually called like maybe when you're trying to do reporting, etc, so I always like to do that same as widget name here.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): Type in the URL.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): The cool website, I guess.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): The open a new tab checkbox here allows us to open.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): This website in a new tab once we click on it, personally I love that feature whenever I open up a new tab or whenever I click on something and it doesn't open a new tab sometimes that bothers me so personally I like to have this checked and then, once again we have.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): The ability to select where we want this.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): will just keep it at the bottom show always create.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): they'll come back and hit refresh.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): And here we go I got that test link.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): Now, if I clicked on this it's going to take me to a page that's unresponsive because it doesn't exist, however, it would it would take you to whatever website you you entered in customs editor.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): Alright, so i'm going to come up here to my test drop down.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): Now I want to show you this i'm going to click three.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): I just want a value in there.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): Because I want to mark this obsolete, so if I come back and I find my.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): let's see.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): test, there are here has dropped down.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): i'm going to come in market obsolete the update we see here.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): With a lot with the strike through and it even says obsolete really good prompt here also has that marked as obsolete, so it indicates quickly at a glance that this field is no longer relevant.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): But if I go back to my project or refresh.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): kind of scroll down, we still have our value.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): Because it was there before it was marked obsolete, but we can see with the strike through here that we're not using this field any longer, so if I go to another another project.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): like this Paris personal Connor they go to their page summary.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): I don't even have that feel any longer right because there wasn't any value in there.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): There is no data if I create a brand new project same thing that will not show up.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): So obsolete is like deleting the field.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): Except it's protecting the data that's already there.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): This remove section button.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): it's actually not going to remove the section all right, so if this was a brand new section like I barely just created it and I didn't put data anywhere in any of the fields.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): Then, yes, I can rule, the section, with no problems, but if I were to try, because it wants to remove all of the fields and widgets it's going to give me this ever they can't because there's actually a lot of live data in those fields.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): So what you do instead of removing a section, because you don't want to lose all of your data, this is an operational system of record right, we want to keep record of everything that we have, so instead of deleting we'll just mark this, as always, hidden.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): So any current projects like correct and existing projects and any future projects will not have this section.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): Alright, so it lets us know that it's hiding all of the data, including reports and searching until you change this back.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): Alright, so always hidden is a safe delete like it's a very soft delete I guess you could say.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): The last thing about sections that I want to show here are going to be these arrows if I wanted to push intake to the top.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): I can do that i'm just moving these sections around with the up and down arrows right.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): Maybe I decided to take was actually better than the fourth spot perfect i'll put parties below it.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): That leads to together.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): And that sections in firefight.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): And once again don't hesitate.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): To ask any questions in the chat there.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): or unmute yourself, and you can ask that way as well.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): So with fighters the vitals and phases and folders like the rest of this is going to be a brief, I promise, this is probably going to be the easiest training that you've had in file line.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): For vitals once again to reiterate that's what we're looking at up here in your case.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): In this blue banner at the top right, so the case number intake owner primary attorney festival dates.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): We can see those all here.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): If I want to create a new vital.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): i'm going to click create new vital.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): click into this Gray bar or the little search button both work.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): And then look for that field.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): Right.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): super simple if you know the name of the field and you don't want to search for it in this way.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): You can just type it out here and click select.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): One of the pro tips that I want to give you today is going to be like a copy paste.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): So if i'm in my case over here my project and.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): Maybe I want this co counsel field to be one of my vitals for some reason I can go ahead and hit command C or control see if you're on PC.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): Because we want to copy that and then we'll paste it to click select.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): And then it finds it for us.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): Then I can go ahead and hit okay.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): Before I do I want to point out, right here, we see case summary, this is letting us know where the Co counsel field is located, so if you have two fields that are very similar to co counsel like maybe one had co counsel with two question marks, but it was in the intake right.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): This is just helping us to be 100% sure and certain that we're selecting the right field.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): We also get that indicator up here the category changed the case summary, we see the field is highlighted we click OK.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): Once we have our field, we have the ability to override the title.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): So maybe instead I don't want that question mark.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): So it'll display like this and my vitals.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): And then I can make a contingent on a section.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): So maybe I only want this vital to show.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): When will say workers COMP is visible.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): we'll go ahead and hit save.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): Now, if I go back to my project and refresh.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): Our vitals are going to change because that workers COMP section is hidden So if I come down to manage sections because workers COMP is one of my FLEX sections.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): I can turn that on it, save and then we'll notice in our vitals we have that co-counsel vital now finally populate.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): That, if I go back in and turn it off.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): same thing, but opposite right that takes itself off of my violence.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): So that's making something or making your vitals contingent on a specific section.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): If you want to remove a vital Of course you can just remove it, that simple.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): Just like in our sections, you can click on these arrows to move your vitals around.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): And then the last bit of information is you can only have 15 vitals at a time, once you hit 15 this create new vital box will no longer be available.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): And you'll either have to just come in here and remove the different vitals so you can change them out or just select the different field, however, you want to do that, but 15 is your Max.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): Another reason why you might want to use this title override is for things like so well right statute of limitations do could be kind of a mouthful so so i'll do.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): looks a little bit better up here.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): or even with primary attorney last first.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): Maybe I come up here and just have primary attorney.
Right.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): I think that'll look a lot better.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): perfect.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): that's vitals.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): Great vital select the field give it a new title, if you want, and then click save.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): phases, is going to be the same thing.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): If you want to create a new face to create face give it a name.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): It took forever for me to even put test in that phase name that's super creative today, as you can tell this choose section area is how we can make this space contingent on a section as well, just like our vitals.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): We can make this contingent on any section that we want right maybe the intake section.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): of your medical section right.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): Now i'm picking these and it's giving me this like this, not a warning but kind of a note that the medical section or the intake sections are always visible, so this isn't really going to help us much in this case.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): at making this contingent on the medical section.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): That, but we still have that option if we wanted to.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): So when you hit save the phase will automatically be put at the top here, though I can click and drag this phase to push it anywhere, I want to.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): If I click into it, I have the ability to rename it make a contingent on it section and remove it.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): I do want you to note this.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): When you click remove face.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): This morning is actually pretty important.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): PowerPoint is asking or letting us know that when we remove this phase we're removing all associated tasks.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): With this phase.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): So if you have a task flow setup.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): And you have these tasks to be triggered based on what phase you're in.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): And I removed this phase those tasks are also going to be removed.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): From task flow So be careful when removing phases note that you're also removing associated tasks.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): So in task flow and you'll learn this in your task flow training, you also have the ability to see your phases, create new phases edit them.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): And when you click on one see like treatment complete on this right hand side you'll see a list of all of the tasks associated with it.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): Here in customs editor we don't see that list so we don't know.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): Exactly what we're removing.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): Right, we might not be 100% sure what's associated to what phase.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): So I don't like to recommend removing phases here and customs editor if you're going to remove phases do that and task flow.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): And again you'll go over that in more detail in your tactical training.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): folders.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): What we're doing here in folders is.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): Updating our template.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): The folder structure in our docs section and how that looks if I come to my project.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): Some of these are ones that i've done one offs for.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): Right like this redacted documents some bait stamp documents they're not going to be.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): In my folder template.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): What we're doing is updating.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): All future folder structures.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): All right, so anything that we change here or add So if I were to add.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): deposition folder up here, I already have the demos right, but just we'll just do test because i'm blanking on a good example I add this test folder I click save because I want to save when I make any changes in my folder template.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): If we go back to my project and refresh I don't have that testable.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): we're not making changes to the folder structure on existing projects.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): we're only making changes for future projects.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): And the same goes with deleting folders So if I were to delete not just this test folder but if I were to delete the discovery folder.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): And hit save i'm going to remember discovery, so I want to bring that one back.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): Go back to my project.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): So this one actually had only a discovery docs folder but if discovery alone were here.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): That wouldn't have been removed right, I never had I created this project before I created the folder structure, which is why not all of these a lot like they let they don't line up very well.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): But it just goes to show that anything we do up here will not affect current projects.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): Only future projects.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): If you wanted to create a sub folder within one of these folders such as maybe fusion.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): I could do like word fusion and then maybe I also want excel fusion.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): There we go, so now we have some sub folders.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): And I can keep going.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): Make lots of Sub folders here.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): I don't believe there's a limit as to how many samples, you can have when I did my testing I got up to 30 before I got incredibly bored and thought there's no way anybody's gonna have 30 except boulders.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): and honestly you shouldn't right it's completely up to you how you want to do this, maybe don't tell everybody in your company or your firm that you can have unlimited sub folders because they might go crazy with creating a new folder path you might not want that so.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): That the fewer the better right, so what i'm doing now is i'm trying to remove the sub folders and I can do that, one by one, or if I want to remove just maybe this sub folder and all the ones below it.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): I can click on the exit the top sub folder.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): And there we go.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): If I need to rename a folder I just click on this pencil.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): Up doesn't look like it wants to rename it right now.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): There we go it's because I didn't save it, yet I can't rename something that wasn't didn't exist.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): So now, I can rename this to anything I want.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): perfect example.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): But I can have that my folder structure.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): If you wanted to place if you might have wondered what this client first name is, this is a replacement field.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): So you can use all of these available replace the fields to be part of your folders name.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): Alright, so you do is your just highlight this year.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): It copy so command C control see.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): Then I can just come in and.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): paste it in.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): This one up here at the top.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): This is your project folder.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): So every single project is going to have that and that's this right here shawn Spencer verse Burt custer.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): Your project folder is going to be the name of your project.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): And if your project doesn't have a name.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): This folder will just take on the name of your client So whoever the main contact is this case.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): that's the folder is going to be named.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): When you're creating your template this field.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): cannot be deleted.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): folder new can't be blank right and then up here, it says the projects top level folder name must contain one of these.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): So the name the client name project ID or unique key.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): That needs to be one of those replacement fields.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): alright.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): When we do make changes, you have to say, all right, please, please, please remember to save.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): We can't even navigate away it lets us know that I have unsafe folder changes.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): So I have to either cancel save it.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): or like, if I were to try to leave here.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): I can press continue without saving.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): But, of course, I always highly recommend just click save.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): they'll hit cancel.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): hit save if you don't want to lose any of your unsafe changes.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): That is.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): Customs editor.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): You can remove this folder template I don't recommend doing that, especially after you've already created your template.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): Simply because you're basically removing all of these folders and all of your hardware all right we're getting rid of all of it so unless you're starting completely from scratch, I would just go in and remove individual folders.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): and add new ones.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): So we went over sections, how to create them create fields and widgets we went over vitals.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): And we understand that we can have only up to 15 vitals before we're cut off.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): phases, you can have as many as you want.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): But don't remove phases.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): Unless you're doing that in task flow.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): And then the folder structure we're not changing the folder structure on existing projects.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): But future projects only.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): This session has been recorded and I will get this out to each one of you that, as well as those that signed up and work in attendance, so if you know any of them, you can put their mind at ease they're getting a copy as well.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): that'll be in the next maybe 30 minutes to an hour, depending on how long it takes to upload the file that you all have been wonderful once again my name is brigham and I hope you have a great rest of your week.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): and feel free to hang out and ask any questions that you might have.
keyla: I have a question for.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): Kelly yeah go ahead.
keyla: yeah I was wondering, is there any way to integrate folders in with your network.
keyla: And reason being that when you have five online it's slower to upload.
keyla: versus if you have it, integrated with your own network.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): So Have you already gone through the migration process.
keyla: yeah where we've been here for.
keyla: quite a long time, but.
keyla: But it's more of a new staff, when we get stuff in litigation and it's a PDF if it's a if it's a bigger PDF then it's.
keyla: Then it takes a really long time to download it and read it readily easier to get it from our own network versus file by where it's stored in the cloud.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): Right and that's, the only thing that I would be able to bring up is that we are cloud based whereas your work.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): was like he isn't cloud based right, so it would be very difficult for them to communicate to each other, I could, I would say, maybe bring it up with your implementation consultant to see if we do have an integration for it, but I really don't think that that's that's possibility.
keyla: Okay.
keyla: Okay, and then I had a question did you go over the the difference between a static and a static page in the.
keyla: Section.
Yes.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): Good question so for static versus collection.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): If I click the custom here.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): If you want it to be a static section, which is something like rk summary where it's just a page full of fields and widgets.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): And then you'll click of course or you will just leave this blank, but if you want it to be a collection section, such as the insurance or the medical where you have this add an item button.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): Because you can continue to add items throughout your cases.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): lifespan right for the case summary or the intake you might fill it out once or twice.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): And kind of just be done with it, so if you want something like.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): A medical section, or even like a parties section or your expenses were to just continuously updating and adding new information.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): that's when I would choose collection.
keyla: Okay, I guess, I guess, my my question was more like is there a way, so you know how like an intake has its own.
keyla: own information, but if we wanted something like in the key summary that had the same information and intake instead of having to have two different fields to collect same thing is there any way to kind of have it to somebody move change in an intake it'll change it in.
keyla: Another another tab.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): So every field is going to be unique.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): And so that is it something that's going to be.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): Possible so you can't have the same field in both the intake advocate summary.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): So I would suggest just if you're going to have it just take it out of one of them.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): and leave it in the other section so maybe just leave it in the case summary and take it out of the intake That would be my off the top of my head kind of solution for that.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): But of course yeah Do you still keep them top contact with your consultant.
keyla: yeah I do.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): Okay, because they'd probably work, a lot more closely with this than I do with our clients.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): So I would get with them and ask maybe what they've seen work in the past, if that's the route you're trying to go and maybe they had some other clients that that one of the same thing and so maybe they found a better solution than then my little quick fix you know.
keyla: And one question.
keyla: there any way that you know how you have the total policies that you can look up the whole total policy is there any way that that in place, it can it can do my total policy basically divide.
keyla: Have a ratio of how much medical expenses you've had that the client has spent versus total policy limits, just to see what that.
keyla: ratio is because we don't want to go over certain amount, where you know you're going to get policy limits, but it's not going to have you know, like you want to know what percentage of a matter of positive elements, you have spent already.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): So I.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): don't know a lot of legal terms, here, but I think I know what you're talking about So if I go to my custom editor.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): I think what you're talking about is a.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): Calculated section calculated field, so if I go to my will say let's go to medical.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): I can give you an example here.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): let's see my widgets I have one called.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): let's see where we.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): Post production and it's a calculating a currency right, so my calculated type, you can do a percentage as well.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): But the formula is going to be the different fields so for mine it's the amount minus the different payments that have been made right the p I P, the php the write offs and the time payments.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): So whatever those fields have if I go to my medical section.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): Do right here my MED payment client payment php write off all are going to take that amount of 5000 and such subtracted to get this number, so if I put in like 600 from the plant payment, we see that get updated the 3700 will pretend, this is 500.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): will see it get updated 35 right.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): So it's going to continually update, for us, I think this is what you're talking about is that right.
keyla: something along these lines percentage.
keyla: Right and a percentage, based on the total policy limits.
keyla: Based on the insurance portion of it, where you can put like you know policy them, it says will be 25 and 25 we have 550 thousand you know, like maybe you don't want to go over 35,000 because going over 35,000 is a spinner.
keyla: it's it's not worth it, because you still already have the positive limited someone in the other.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): Okay, so I I would play around with that calculated percentage you'd have to have other fields, in that I guess the policy limit section or wherever that's located.
keyla: I think you said insurance section.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): yeah wherever that's located for you, I would just kind of find those like here's the policy limit right if I put in a big number, you said what 300,000 or something 35,000.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): I don't know why that just happened.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): That yes man, I will definitely make sure that this recording gets to you.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): So there's 3500 we got the final coverage policy number I don't know what else I mean this is just a test environments, which probably doesn't look exactly like what you might have.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): What you're wanting to do.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): I would suggest we take it offline and go over it, probably with your ic because i'm hundred percent sure.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): that this question is very common.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): Okay, that you're you're definitely not the only one that has gone over this, so I would reach out to them and just try to get that calculated field, I I really feel like it's a calculated field here, but as a trader I don't really go over builds I just.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): How to.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): Use the system really.
keyla: yeah cuz it's a calculated field within insurance policies and medical ton of medical expenses.
keyla: that's an end it's just I guess it integrates with two different ones where you have you know insurances and collection one and and the medical as well.
keyla: But you want to add both of the insurance and then both of the medical and then have that total number.
keyla: have its own ratio.
keyla: that's just.
keyla: that's just what I mean.
keyla: I mean I.
keyla: I mean I manually do it, I run the reports and based on that I just have to run an excel and from there just see where I need to focus on.
keyla: But.
keyla: that's my way.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): I want to say good luck, I do want to give you just the direction to take, which is to contact gracie see if they can help you build that out.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): I wish I can help further.
keyla: So, when you say our person would that be the person who sells the product by the that he gets in contact with every once a year, or I can get in contact with them once a year.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): It would be the consultant that helped you launch.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): Okay, you can ask anybody on on the file inside your account manager your.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): asm or a CSM sorry i'm sure they'll be able to also get you to the right person.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): Okay.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): But yeah I don't want to leave you empty handed, but at least we I think got the right direction, going for you.
I do appreciate your questions.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): alright.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): Well, thanks kayla.
Thanks man and thanks Scott.
Brigham Jenkins (the case system): Have a good rest of your days.